It's 6:00 a.m. on a Monday. I just woke
up. I wanted to sleep in, but I have a
lot I want to accomplish today. Let's be
productive.
First, I'm going to brush my teeth.
These days, I go to the gym first thing
in the morning, so I'm going to change
into my workout clothes.
I need some energy for the gym, so I'm
going to make a pre-workout snack. I
almost always have coffee and a banana,
but I'm out of bananas right now, so I
think I'm going to make a rice cake.
And there we go. Some carbs for energy
before the gym. I have leftover coffee
from yesterday. Let's see [music] how it
tastes.
Mhm.
It's a little watered-down, but it'll do
the trick. I always keep a stack of
Sudoku puzzles at my table. [music] I
love doing them while I eat. It helps me
relax and keeps me from going on my
phone.
I'm filling up my water bottle and then
I'm heading out.
Let's go.
I love my walk to the gym. There's
hardly ever any people out at this time,
so it's very peaceful. The weather today
is beautiful. It's going to be a
gorgeous day.
Today, I'm focusing on my upper body,
especially my back. I'm trying to grow
my lats because my New Year's resolution
was to get a pull-up this year. I'm
going to start with some dynamic
stretches.
Let's just try a pull-up and see if I've
made any progress. Don't judge me.
That was humbling. Zero progress.
>> [music]
>> I'm going to do lat pull-downs now. I'm
going to do three sets of 10 reps.
Could you see my back gains when I did
those?
Look how red my cheeks are. I'm [music]
dripping sweat. Got to stay hydrated.
Let's work on my six-pack and finish up
with abs.
I don't know if my form on those is any
good, but I heard they get you shredded,
so I'm going to keep trying them. I'm
skipping cardio.
I walk a lot throughout the day, so that
counts.
My groceries got delivered. I'm going to
put my groceries away.
It feels good having a fully stocked
fridge. No coupon eats this week.
I've got a few meetings this morning, so
I'm going to take a shower and get ready
for the day. I just got out of the
shower [music]
and I'm starting with skin care, of
course.
My makeup is done. I'm going to throw on
some clothes and make [music] a quick
breakfast. Here is today's final look. I
kept it simple with a claw clip today
because I couldn't be bothered to style
my hair. I have about 30 minutes [music]
before my first meeting starts, so I'm
going to make one of my favorite
breakfasts. Spray the pan,
throw in some garlic. I use a measuring
cup and do [music] a half cup of frozen
spinach. I'm adding a cup of liquid egg
whites.
Don't mix it. Just [music] let it sit
and I'm going to add some salt and
pepper. When the top is still wet,
[music] put one tortilla right on top.
While that's cooking, I'm going to slice
up some avocado.
Oh, it's beautiful.
I'm going to use the side without the
pit. It's [music] time to flip this.
Let's see if I can do it without [music]
making a mess.
Ooh, that was good.
I love this wrap so much. It gets nice
[music] and crispy on the outside.
Mhm, it's so [music] quick and easy and
super healthy.
I'm about to start my first meeting of
the day. It's a one-on-one meeting with
Virginia. She helps me out a lot with
content.
Hi, good morning. So sorry I'm a little
late.
>> Oh, it's fine. It's
>> Before we start, just a FYI, I'm
recording right now.
>> Oh, okay. Okay.
>> Yeah, just a heads-up. So, let's get
into it. First of all, the worksheet,
baseball was posted last night. So, the
files and everything you need for that
are already up. So, that's good to go.
And then, shorts, this is like our first
week doing the double posting. Let's see
how that goes. Do you need anything from
me still for that?
>> I think you said you were working on
like one more over the weekend or
something.
>> I will keep you updated on those and let
you know.
>> [music]
>> Yeah, let's wrap it up, I guess, then.
And I'll see you at 11:00. Bye-bye.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> It's about time for meeting number two.
This one is our weekly team meeting. The
cameraman is leading it.
>> Me?
>> [laughter]
>> Are you ready?
>> Uh I'm in a rush.
>> Okay. First of all, I guess let's talk
about the long form [music] that we
uploaded.
Okay, thank you, guys. Bye-bye.
Wow, I'm exhausted. That meeting took
forever. The boss wouldn't stop yapping.
>> Hey.
>> [laughter]
>> The goal is to film four videos today.
That's a big goal. My first video will
be a lecture. It's for my VOD series.
So, check it out.
Welcome back. Today, you'll
Today, you'll learn common expressions
used by native speakers all the time.
I am starving, so I'm making tuna rice
bowls for the cameraman and I. I use
microwave rice, but this one is kind of
special because it has lentils in it. I
use about half of one pack and I put in
some edamame as well. Here, half in
there. That's a lot of fiber.
You got to have the kimpch. That's
kimchi for short. Kimpch. I just made
that up.
Okay, lunch is served. These days, I'm
watching Heart Signal, but there's only
one episode weekly, so I'm going to try
watching [music]
Nannun Solo for the first time ever. I'm
hoping [music] it helps me with my
Korean.
Video two of four today. I'm filming a
vlog for my VOD series, but it's
basically a voiceover. So, hopefully
it's pretty quick and easy. Last year, I
set one of my friends up on a blind date
with my co-worker.
And cut.
Okay, then I'm just like
>> Mhm?
>> It's fine.
>> It's okay.
>> [laughter]
[music]
>> I'm going to be honest, I'm losing
steam. I've been laying in bed and
scrolling on my phone for the past
[music] 20 minutes, but this is a
productivity vlog, so [music] I need to
get moving.
>> [bell]
[laughter]
>> Leave me alone.
>> We're supposed to be having a productive
Monday.
>> I worked too hard.
>> [snorts]
>> I came out for a walk. I got to get my
steps in and hopefully this gives me
some energy.
The last thing we're filming today is a
short-form video. It's a TikTok trend
these days. You say one phrase in four
different tones. We're going to say
[music] "Good for you." using four
different tones. It should be fun.
Good for you.
>> Good for you.
>> [laughter]
>> That was good.
Yeah.
I'm about to hop on a call for my final
meeting of the day. It's with an English
company in Japan about a potential
collab. Hello.
I know this morning I said no more
Coupang Eats, but hear me out. I was
just too busy today and didn't have time
to prep dinner. So,
I caved.
This place is pretty healthy though.
It's kind of like my go-to delivery
spot.
It's like a chicken doshirak. So, it
comes with roast chicken, rice, some
kimchi, a bunch of vegetables. They even
give you
this really delicious egg drop soup that
I'm obsessed with. So, yes, I did get
delivery food, but I'm not going to feel
too guilty about it. I'm just going to
enjoy it. What's crazy to me is that all
of this food was less than 9,000 Korean
won. That's a lot of food. I have a
guest joining [music] me for dinner
tonight.
How was your day today?
>> Me?
>> Mhm.
>> Busy, Monday, tired.
>> What was your high and low today?
[music] I know your high was spending
time with me.
No comment?
>> Can we eat?
>> Wow. [laughter]
Wow.
>> Taking a walk with you.
>> Good answer. Good answer. [music]
Low?
>> Low?
>> Mhm.
>> There's no such a low.
>> [laughter]
>> Living with you.
>> Oh my
I feel sick now. What was my high?
[music]
I felt like we had a lot of productive
meetings today. So, that was a high. My
low was being humbled by my pull-up
[music] at the gym. I might delete that
footage. That was pretty bad.
>> I'm not deleting that. So, don't worry.
>> I got to eat more protein to get
stronger. Cheers.
>> Cheers.
>> It's 8:40 and there's still a few things
that I want to accomplish tonight.
First, I want to reach 10,000 steps. I'm
only at like 5,500
right now. I'm only like halfway there.
I'm also writing a new book, so I want
to work on it and finish maybe two
chapters tonight. So, I'm going to write
and walk on my walking pad to kill two
birds with one stone.
I hit my step count. Woo! I did not
finish two chapters of my book, but I
made some progress and that's what's
important. Now, I'm just going to do the
dishes and get ready for bed because I
have had a long, full day.
You want to give me give you hand.
>> [laughter]
>> Feel free to step in.
That's my man.
Thanks, babe.
>> You're welcome.
>> It's time to take my makeup off.
>> [music]
>> I'm all tucked in and ready for bed.
Thanks for spending [music]
a busy and productive Monday with me.
Bringing you guys along helped [music]
keep me accountable. I hope you had a
great start to your week, too. Good
night.